https://vividoptical.com.au/privacy-policy

Vivid OpticalEyewearDesigner FramesIc! BerlinMichel Henau EyewearAnne & ValentinPrada Designer GlassesBulgari Designer GlassesVersace Designer GlassesDolce & Gabbana Designer GlassesTiffany Designer GlassesFurla Designer GlassesCarter Bond EyewearPro Design Danish EyewearSilhouette EyewearCoach Designer GlassesCaroline AbramAdidas EyewearMasunaga EyewearSunglassesPaul Taylor Designer EyewearMaui Jim SunglassesDolce & Gabbana Designer SunglassesPrada Designer GlassesRay-Ban Designer SunglassesAdidas SunglassesVersace Designer SunglassesVogue EyewearTiffany Designer SunglassesChildren's EyewearYoupi!oio Children's EyewearAdidas Kids EyewearDutz Kidz EyewearMarco Polo Kids EyewearCaroline Abram Tête à LunettesEye HealthWhy have your eyes tested?Latest eye testing technologyCommon causes of poor visionChildren's VisionOrtho-KCorneal TopographyDigital Eye StrainMyopia ControlIrritable or Dry EyesRed and painful eyesDiabetic eye diseaseMacular degenerationGlaucomaCataractsOCT - The latest technologyContact LensesContact LensesContact Lenses and Overnight WearContact Lenses for over 40sAbout usOptometry Service & SupportThe People at Vivid OpticalPayment OptionsWebsite Privacy PolicyNewsContact UsThankyou for your Message
EyewearDesigner FramesIc! BerlinMichel Henau EyewearAnne & ValentinPrada Designer GlassesBulgari Designer GlassesVersace Designer GlassesDolce & Gabbana Designer GlassesTiffany Designer GlassesFurla Designer GlassesCarter Bond EyewearPro Design Danish EyewearSilhouette EyewearCoach Designer GlassesCaroline AbramAdidas EyewearMasunaga EyewearSunglassesPaul Taylor Designer EyewearMaui Jim SunglassesDolce & Gabbana Designer SunglassesPrada Designer GlassesRay-Ban Designer SunglassesAdidas SunglassesVersace Designer SunglassesVogue EyewearTiffany Designer SunglassesChildren's EyewearYoupi!oio Children's EyewearAdidas Kids EyewearDutz Kidz EyewearMarco Polo Kids EyewearCaroline Abram Tête à LunettesEye HealthWhy have your eyes tested?Latest eye testing technologyCommon causes of poor visionChildren's VisionOrtho-KCorneal TopographyDigital Eye StrainMyopia ControlIrritable or Dry EyesRed and painful eyesDiabetic eye diseaseMacular degenerationGlaucomaCataractsOCT - The latest technologyContact LensesContact LensesContact Lenses and Overnight WearContact Lenses for over 40sAbout usOptometry Service & SupportThe People at Vivid OpticalPayment OptionsNewsContact Us
Website Privacy Policy
Sharpe & Fowler is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Sharpe & Fowler Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Sharpe & Fowler website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
Sharpe & Fowler may collect personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Sharpe & Fowler may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your post code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Sharpe & Fowler. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Sharpe & Fowler for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Sharpe & Fowler Web site.
Sharpe & Fowler encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Sharpe & Fowler so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Sharpe & Fowler is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Sharpe & Fowler and Sharpe & Fowler family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
Sharpe & Fowler collects and uses your personal information to operate the Sharpe & Fowler Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Sharpe & Fowler also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Sharpe & Fowler and its affiliates. Sharpe & Fowler may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
Sharpe & Fowler does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Sharpe & Fowler may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Sharpe & Fowler may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Sharpe & Fowler, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Sharpe & Fowler does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
Sharpe & Fowler keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Sharpe & Fowler, in order to determine what Sharpe & Fowler services are the most popular. This data may be used to deliver customized content and advertising within Sharpe & Fowler to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Sharpe & Fowler Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice and in compliance with the Commonwealth Privacy Act 1988, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to or comply with legal process served on Sharpe & Fowler or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Sharpe & Fowler; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Sharpe & Fowler, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Sharpe & Fowler Web site may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalise Sharpe & Fowler pages, or register with Sharpe & Fowler site or services, a cookie helps Sharpe & Fowler to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Sharpe & Fowler Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Sharpe & Fowler features that you customised.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Sharpe & Fowler services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
Sharpe & Fowler secures your personal information from unauthorised access, use or disclosure. Sharpe & Fowler secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
Sharpe & Fowler will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Sharpe & Fowler encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Sharpe & Fowler is protecting your information.
Contact Information
Sharpe & Fowler welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Sharpe & Fowler has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Sharpe & Fowler at info@sharpeandfowler.com.au. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Follow us on Instagram
8
| 1
15
| 0
10
| 1
23
